<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SeahawkTours</string>
    <string name="cis_info">The Computer Information Systems (CIS) building was constructed to house the Information Systems
        and Operations Management Department from the Cameron School of Business and the Department of Computer Science from
        the College of Arts and Sciences. The CIS Building, a new 51,731 square-foot state-of-the-art facility on the UNCW campus,
        opened January 10, 2007 for the new school semester. Work on the facility began on July 29, 2004 with the groundbreaking,
        and competed in December of 2006. The building cost approximately $12.8 million and was funded by the North Carolina State
        Bond campaign of 2000.</string>
    <string name="bear_info">Bear Hall opened at its present site in 1972 as the home for the Business and Economics Departments.
        Currently, the Departments of Computer Science, Mathematics and Statistics, and Philosophy and Religion occupy classrooms,
        teaching labs and faculty offices.The College of Arts and Science also resides here. As the inscription on the plaque states
        Bear Hall is named for,"The original Isaac Bear Building, located at Market and 13th Streets, served as the first home of Wilmington College,outside the public school system.Classes were first held there in 1947."
        </string>
    <string name="fisher_info">Groundbreaking for the Herbert and Sylvia Fisher Student Center occurred on August 18, 2004,
        and two years later on August 24, 2006, UNCW celebrated the grand opening of the Herbert and Sylvia Fisher Student Center.
        The 70,536 square feet, two-story, center includes a 350 seat, big screen, movie theatre (the Lumina Theatre), a two-story bookstore,
        a new game room, and a new Varsity Café which features decor and memorabilia from the original Varsity Café. The center also houses a
        beautiful indoor lighted waterfall named “Rebirth” which was a gift of the UNCW class of 2005-2006. The new building is connected to the
        Fisher University Union by covered colonnades and is located between the old Union and Westside Hall. The project cost a total of $31 million
        and was funded by student fees. </string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="CIS">CIS Building</string>
    <string name="Bear">Bear Hall</string>
    <string name="Fisher">Fisher Student Center</string>

</resources>
